<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<Studios>
    <Studio>
        <Name>Studio 1</Name>
        <Country>Contry of Studios</Country>
        <Year>1989</Year>
        <History>American motion picture studio based at The Walt Disney Studios in Burbank, California and is a subsidiary of Walt Disney Studios, itself a wholly owned division of The Walt Disney Company, with film producer Kevin Feige serving as president.[3] Previously, the studio was a subsidiary of Marvel Entertainment until The Walt Disney Company reorganized the companies in August 2015.</History>
    </Studio>
    <Studio>
        <Name>Studio 2</Name>
        <Country>Contry of Studios</Country>
        <Year>2012</Year>
        <History>American film production label of Warner Bros. Entertainment that was founded in 1967 by Robert Shaye as a film distribution company, later becoming an independent film studio. It became a subsidiary of the Turner Broadcasting System in 1994 before Turner merged with Time Warner in 1996, and was later merged with its larger sister studio Warner Bros. Entertainment in 2008. Currently, its films are distributed by Warner Bros.</History>
    </Studio>
    <Studio>
        <Name>Studio 3</Name>
        <Country>Country of Studio 3</Country>
        <Year>1800</Year>
        <History>American film studio based in Hollywood, California, that has been a subsidiary of the American media conglomerate Viacom since 1994. Paramount is the fifth oldest surviving film studio in the world,[2] the second oldest in the United States, and the sole member of the "Big Six" film studios still located in the Los Angeles neighborhood of Hollywood.</History>
    </Studio>
    <Studio>
        <Name>Studio 4</Name>
        <Country>Country of Studio 4</Country>
        <Year>2007</Year>
        <History>The Ramoji Film City in India is located in Hyderabad. At 2000 acres, it is the largest integrated film city in the Telangana and the largest studio complex in the world. The film city was also certified by the Guinness World Records as the world’s largest Film Studio complex. It was set up by Ramoji Group in 1996. It is also a popular tourism and recreation centre, containing natural and artificial attractions including an amusement park. Around 1.5 million tourists visit the place every year.</History>
    </Studio>
</Studios>
